O.W. Riegel Papers WLU.Coll.0387
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
- Journalism Department, 1932-1974; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 8.8 Linear Feet This series is primarily contained in large and medium size archival storage boxes. Additionally, there are two boxes of Newspaper Clippings related to the Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation and other aspects of th
  - Course Materials, 1932-1974 (Box 3-7, Folder 186-372, Box 11-13, Folder 508-520)
    - Roll Books, 1967-1973 (Box 12, Folder 519)
    - Roll Books, 1967-1973 (Box 12, Folder 520)
  - Journalist Recruitment, 1932-1974 (Box 8, Folder 373-377)
    Items in this subseries consist of discussions between the Journalism Department and outside news industries about job availability and the desire for higher quality recruits. Riegel points the low quality towards a national issue of low incentives for high quality students in the Journalism field.
    - Journalism Recruitment, 1955 (Folder 373)
    - Journalism Recruitment Jan.-Oct., 1956 (Folder 374)
    - Journalism Recruitment Oct.-Nov., 1956 (Folder 375)
    - Journalism Recruitment, 1959 (Folder 376)
    - Journalism Recruitment Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 377)
  - Lee Editorial Award, 1932-1974 (Box 8, Folder 378-381)
    the Lee Editorial Award was a prize for what the award's judges thought was the best editorial in a given year based on nominations by editors, newspapers, and publishers. Items in this subseries focus on informing the public about the award, statements by award winners, and the announcement of award winners.
    - Lee Editorial Award, 1938-1941 (Folder 378)
    - Lee Editorial Award, 1956 (Folder 379)
    - Lee Editorial Award, 1956 (Folder 380)
    - Lee Editorial Award, 1957-1959 (Folder 381)
  - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation, 1932-1974 (Box 8, Folder 382-427)
    The Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation was an institution that sought to share the history of Journalism at Washington and Lee through a variety of publications, news stories and events. Items of note in this subseries include a scrapbook of journalism department activites from the mid 1950s and small posters of different journalism department events on campus.
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Pre, 1930-1931 (Folder 382)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation, 1931-1932 (Folder 383)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1932-1935 (Folder 384)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1936-1940 (Folder 385)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation, 1940-1941 (Folder 386)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation, 1941-1947 (Folder 387)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1947-1948 (Folder 388)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1950-1952 (Folder 389)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1952-1953 (Folder 390)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Photos, 1952-1953 (Folder 391)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Photos, 1952-1953 (Folder 392)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1953-1955 (Folder 393)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1955-1956 (Folder 394)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1956-1957 (Folder 395)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1958-1959 (Folder 396)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1959-1960 (Folder 397)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1960-1961 (Folder 398)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1961-1962 (Folder 399)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Photos, 1961-1962 (Folder 400)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1962-1963 (Folder 401)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1963-1964 (Folder 402)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1965 (Folder 403)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1965 (Folder 404)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1965-1967 (Folder 405)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1967-1968 (Folder 406)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1968 (Folder 407)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation:, 1968 (Folder 408)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Copy Right Forms A-E, 1932-1974 (Folder 409)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Copy Right Forms E-U, 1932-1974 (Folder 410)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Ame-Ful, 1932-1974 (Folder 411)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Gaines, 1937-1942 (Folder 412)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Gaines, 1942-1946 (Folder 413)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Gri-Hod, 1932-1974 (Folder 414)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Hol-Joh, 1932-1974 (Folder 415)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Lauck, 1932-1974 (Folder 416)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Ley-Rat, 1932-1974 (Folder 417)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Sho-Tuc, 1932-1974 (Folder 418)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence U.S. N-Web, 1932-1974 (Folder 419)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Correspondence Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 420)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Photos, 1947 (Folder 421)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Staff Applications, 1932-1974 (Folder 422)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Staff Dure, 1932-1974 (Folder 423)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Staff Gelatt, 1957-1959 (Folder 424)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Staff Gelatt & Patchin, 1932-1974 (Folder 425)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 426)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation: Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 427)
    - Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation, 1939-1948 (Box 12, Folder 521)
  - Library, 1932-1974 (Box 8, Folder 428-430)
    During Riegel's tenure as a professor, the Journalism Department kept its own library for students to use. Items in this subseries consist of correspondence and materials related to the library's everyday function.
    - Library, 1941-1954 (Folder 427)
    - Library, 1955-1958 (Folder 428)
    - Library, 1959-1964 (Folder 429)
  - Mass Media Booknotes, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 431-439)
    Mass Media Booknotes was a publication that reported new publications related to mass media and communications. Items within this series consist of monthly reports on new journalism publications.
    - Mass Media Booknotes, 1971 (Folder 431)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Jan.-Jul., 1972 (Folder 432)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Sep.-Dec., 1972 (Folder 433)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Jan.-Jun., 1973 (Folder 434)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Jul.-De., 1973 (Folder 435)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Jan.-Jun., 1974 (Folder 436)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Jul.-Dec., 1974 (Folder 437)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Jan.-Jun., 1975 (Folder 438)
    - Mass Media Booknotes Jul.-Dec., 1975 (Folder 439)
  - Photos, 1932-1974 (Box 8, Folder 440-449)
    - Photos, 1930-1947 (Folder 440)
    - Photos, 1946-1947 (Folder 441)
    - Photos, 1948-1949 (Folder 442)
    - Photos, 1949-1951 (Folder 443)
    - Photos, 1951-1952 (Folder 444)
    - Photos Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 445)
    - Photos Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 446)
    - Photos Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 447)
    - Photos Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 448)
    - Photos Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 449)
  - Publicity, 1932-1974 (Box 8-9, Folder 450-463, Box 12-13, Folder 522-526)
    Publicity regarding the Journalism Department consists of articles in magazines, newspapers, and other media sources that highlight the department's activities. The bulk of items in this subseries consist of articles and press releases related to the Journalism department. Items of note include an article by Riegel titled "The Muted Trumpet" and a Spanish booklet about Nationalism and Communications.
    - Publicity, 1964-1965 (Folder 450)
    - Publicity, 1965 (Folder 451)
    - Publicity, 1965 (Folder 452)
    - Publicity: National Cartoonists society Awards Dinner Program with Signatures, 1965 (Folder 453)
    - Publicity, 1966-1970 (Folder 454)
    - Publicity: Muted Trumpet, 1968 (Folder 455)
    - Publicity: Muted Trumpet, 1968 (Folder 456)
    - Publicity: Muted Trumpet: Correspondence, 1968 (Folder 457)
    - Publicity: Nationalism and Communications, 1968 (Folder 458)
    - Publicity: Nationalism and Communications, 1968 (Folder 459)
    - Publicity: Nationalism and Communications Correspondence, 1968 (Folder 460)
    - Publicity Film Comment, 1969 (Folder 461)
    - Publicity Film Comment, 1969 (Folder 462)
    - Publicity, 1971-1972 (Folder 463)
    - Laboratory Dedication, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 522)
    - Laboratory Dedication Correspondence, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 523)
    - Publicity, 1940-1955 (Box 12, Folder 524)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1947-1965 (Box 13, Folder 525)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1947-1965 (Box 13, Folder 526)
  - Radio, 1950-1970 (Box 9, Folder 464-470)
    Items in this subseries focus on the establishment and early years of WLUR. some events of note include problems with the radio antenna during installation, and program listings from early WLUR broadcasts.
    - Radio, 1961-1967 (Folder 464)
    - Radio, 1972 (Folder 465)
    - Radio, 1972-1982 (Folder 466)
    - Radio Correspondence: Davis, 1961-1982 (Folder 467)
    - Radio Correspondence: G-Win, 1961-1982 (Folder 468)
    - Radio: News, 1961-1982 (Folder 469)
    - Radio Misc., 1961-1982 (Folder 470)
  - Seminars, 1949-1970 (Box 9-10, Folder 471-501)
    This subseries consists of various seminars hosted by the Journalism department including a seminar on editorial writing and one on law in relation to the media. Items of note include the speeches of seminar speakers and seminar programs.
    - Editorial, 1949 (Folder 471)
    - Editorial, 1950-1951 (Folder 472)
    - Editorial, 1953 (Folder 473)
    - Editorial, 1955 (Folder 474)
    - Editorial Correspondence, 1949 (Folder 475)
    - Editorial Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Folder 476)
    - Editorial Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Folder 477)
    - Editorial Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Folder 478)
    - Law Correspondence Ame-Egg, 1932-1974 (Folder 479)
    - Law Correspondence Eichner, 1959-1960 (Folder 480)
    - Law Correspondence Eichner, 1960 (Folder 481)
    - Law Correspondence Far-Hil, 1932-1974 (Folder 482)
    - Law Correspondence Hyn-Mey, 1932-1974 (Folder 483)
    - Law Correspondence Mis-Wig, 1932-1974 (Folder 484)
    - Law Correspondence Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 485)
    - Law Materials, 1932-1974 (Folder 486)
    - Newspaper Management Apr.-Nov., 1952 (Folder 487)
    - Newspaper Management Nov., 1952 (Folder 488)
    - Newspaper Management Misc., 1952 (Folder 489)
    - Newspaper Management Correspondence Bot-Joh, 1932-1974 (Folder 490)
    - Newspaper Management Correspondence Ley-Wal, 1932-1974 (Folder 491)
    - Newspaper Management Correspondence Whi-Wis, 1932-1974 (Folder 492)
    - Newspaper Management Correspondence Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 493)
    - News Photography Conference, 1938-1939 (Folder 494)
    - News Photography Conference, 1939 (Folder 495)
    - Science Service, 1950 (Folder 496)
    - Science Service, 1959-1961 (Folder 497)
    - Science Service, 1961 (Folder 498)
    - Science Service Correspondence Bra-Dev, 1932-1974 (Folder 499)
    - Correspondence Davis, 1932-1974 (Folder 500)
    - CorrespondenceInd-Mar & Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 501)
  - Miscellaneous, 1932-1974 (Box 10, Folder 502-507)
    Items in this subseries are relevant to the journalism department, but do not relate to any of the other subseries. Items of note include a menu at a Sigma Delta Chi dinner, a chart comparing faculty compensation at various universities during the 1970s and a large chart analyzing Virginia daily newspapers.
    - Miscellaneous, 1933-1968 (Folder 502)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969-1978 (Folder 503)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1974 (Folder 504)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1974 (Folder 505)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1974 (Folder 506)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1974 (Folder 507)
  - Unprocessed Materials, 1934-1973 (Box 10a-10d)
- Personal Correspondence, 1926-1991; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); Riegel, Hunt; 3.92 Linear Feet (Box 1-3, Folder 1-224)
  Items in this series pertain to Riegel's personal correspondence between himself and colleagues, friends, and family. Some material is related to or mentions his work, but the majority of the material is about his or other people's personal lives, opinions, and thoughts around world events.
  - Allen, 1929-1991 (Folder 1)
  - Cam-Cantril, 1929-1991 (Folder 2)
  - Cantril, 1929-1991 (Folder 3)
  - Carl-Carr, 1929-1991 (Folder 4)
  - Carv-Cat, 1929-1991 (Folder 5)
  - Cha-Childs, 1929-1991 (Folder 6)
  - Childs, 1929-1991 (Folder 7)
  - Chilton, 1929-1991 (Folder 8)
  - Chit-Ciu, 1929-1991 (Folder 9)
  - Cla, 1929-1991 (Folder 10)
  - Cle-Cli, 1929-1991 (Folder 11)
  - Coc-Com, 1929-1991 (Folder 12)
  - Con-Cowi, 1929-1991 (Folder 13)
  - Cowl-H.Cox, 1929-1991 (Folder 14)
  - Cox, 1929-1991 (Folder 15)
  - Cra-Cre, 1929-1991 (Folder 16)
  - Cro-Cut, 1929-1991 (Folder 17)
  - Dabney, 1929-1991 (Folder 18)
  - Dai-Davis L., 1929-1991 (Folder 19)
  - P. Davis, 1929-1991 (Folder 20)
  - Day-Dev, 1929-1991 (Folder 21)
  - Dew-Dic, 1929-1991 (Folder 22)
  - Dijour, 1929-1991 (Folder 23)
  - Din-Drab, 1929-1991 (Folder 24)
  - Drak-Dye, 1929-1991 (Folder 25)
  - Eagle, 1929-1991 (Folder 26)
  - Eas-Eld, 1929-1991 (Folder 27)
  - Ell-Era, 1929-1991 (Folder 28)
  - Estabrook, 1964-1965 (Folder 29)
  - Estabrook, 1965-1968 (Folder 30)
  - Fal-G.Feyer, 1929-1991 (Folder 31)
  - G. Feyer, 1961-1983 (Folder 32)
  - R. Feyer-Fli, 1929-1991 (Folder 33)
  - Flom, 1929-1991 (Folder 34)
  - Foo-Fox, 1929-1991 (Folder 35)
  - Fral-Frank, 1929-1991 (Folder 36)
  - E. Frank-K. Frank, 1929-1991 (Folder 37)
  - Frantz-Fre, 1929-1991 (Folder 38)
  - Fri-Fur, 1929-1991 (Folder 39)
  - Gaa-Ger, 1929-1991 (Folder 40)
  - Ghi-Gos, 1929-1991 (Folder 41)
  - Gou-Gree, 1929-1991 (Folder 42)
  - Gref-Gun, 1929-1991 (Folder 43)
  - Had-Hane, 1929-1991 (Folder 44)
  - Hann-Har, 1929-1991 (Folder 45)
  - Hay-Hil, 1929-1991 (Folder 46)
  - Hin, 1929-1991 (Folder 47)
  - Hob-Hof, 1929-1991 (Folder 48)
  - Holl-Holt, 1929-1991 (Folder 49)
  - Hop-Hor, 1929-1991 (Folder 50)
  - Hou-How, 1929-1991 (Folder 51)
  - Hub-Hun, 1929-1991 (Folder 52)
  - Hus-Hym, 1929-1991 (Folder 53)
  - Ile-Jac, 1929-1991 (Folder 54)
  - Jandrey, 1929-1991 (Folder 55)
  - Jar-E. Johnson, 1929-1991 (Folder 56)
  - L. Johnson, 1929-1991 (Folder 57)
  - M. Johnson-Jones, 1929-1991 (Folder 58)
  - A. Jones-R. Jones, 1929-1991 (Folder 59)
  - R. Jones, 1965 (Folder 60)
  - Kad-Kaston, 1929-1991 (Folder 61)
  - Kaston, 1982-1983 (Folder 62)
  - Kat-Keefe, 1929-1991 (Folder 63)
  - Keefe, 1979-1989 (Folder 64)
  - Keel-Kel, 1929-1991 (Folder 65)
  - Kempers, 1929-1991 (Folder 66)
  - Kennedy J.-R., 1929-1991 (Folder 67)
  - R. Kennedy-Kim, 1929-1991 (Folder 68)
  - Kip-Kor, 1929-1991 (Folder 69)
  - Kni-Kraft, 1929-1991 (Folder 70)
  - Kraft, 1953-1972 (Folder 71)
  - Kram-Kur, 1929-1991 (Folder 72)
  - Lac-Lan, 1929-1991 (Folder 73)
  - Lar-Lau, 1929-1991 (Folder 74)
  - Lay-LeB, 1929-1991 (Folder 75)
  - Lee-Len, 1929-1991 (Folder 76)
  - Les-Leveque, 1929-1991 (Folder 77)
  - Leverty, 1954-1957 (Folder 78)
  - Leverty, 1957-1961 (Folder 79)
  - Leverty, 1961-1967 (Folder 80)
  - Leverty, 1967-1986 (Folder 81)
  - Leverty Misc., 1929-1991 (Folder 82)
  - Leverty Misc., 1929-1991 (Folder 83)
  - Leverty Misc., 1929-1991 (Folder 84)
  - Levi-Lon, 1929-1991 (Folder 85)
  - Lot-Lun, 1929-1991 (Folder 86)
  - Lyle, 1929-1991 (Folder 87)
  - Mac-Magazine Publishers Association, 1929-1991 (Folder 88)
  - Magazine Publishers Association, 1961-1963 (Folder 89)
  - Mage-Man, 1929-1991 (Folder 90)
  - Marc-Mark, 1929-1991 (Folder 91)
  - Mars-Matk, 1929-1991 (Folder 92)
  - Matt-McD, 1929-1991 (Folder 93)
  - McG-Mei, 1929-1991 (Folder 94)
  - Mer-Mir, 1929-1991 (Folder 95)
  - Mira, 1948-1980 (Folder 96)
  - Mog-Mon, 1929-1991 (Folder 97)
  - D. Moore, 1944-1978 (Folder 98)
  - D. Moore, 1980-1989 (Folder 99)
  - E. Moore-H. Morgan, 1929-1991 (Folder 100)
  - S. Morgan-Morr, 1929-1991 (Folder 101)
  - M. Morten, 1929-1991 (Folder 102)
  - S. Morten-A. Moss, 1929-1991 (Folder 103)
  - J. Moss-Mur, 1929-1991 (Folder 104)
  - Muth, 1929-1991 (Folder 105)
  - Mye, 1929-1991 (Folder 106)
  - Naf-Nat, 1929-1991 (Folder 107)
  - National Committee for an Adequate US Overseas Information Program, 1954-1959 (Folder 108)
  - National Academy of Sciences- National Association for Better Radio and Television, 1929-1991 (Folder 109)
  - National Association of Broadcasters, National Business Publications, National Conference for Editorial Writers, 1929-1991 (Folder 110)
  - National Council of College Publication Advisors-Nelson, 1929-1991 (Folder 111)
  - Nem-Newsw, 1929-1991 (Folder 112)
  - Newsp-H. Newt, 1929-1991 (Folder 113)
  - V. Newt-Noelle-Newmann, 1929-1991 (Folder 114)
  - Noelle-Newman, 1981-1982 (Folder 115)
  - Noelle-Newman, 1982-1988 (Folder 116)
  - Nol-Nyh, 1929-1991 (Folder 117)
  - Oberlaender Trust-Oco, 1929-1991 (Folder 118)
  - O'Ke-Owen, 1929-1991 (Folder 119)
  - Pac-Palm, 1929-1991 (Folder 120)
  - Palu-Par, 1929-1991 (Folder 121)
  - Pax-Penic, 1929-1991 (Folder 122)
  - Penn-Persinger, 1929-1991 (Folder 123)
  - Persinger, 1929-1991 (Folder 124)
  - Pet-Phi, 1929-1991 (Folder 125)
  - Photography, 1961 (Folder 126)
  - Pia-Pla, 1929-1991 (Folder 127)
  - Pog-Poy, 1929-1991 (Folder 128)
  - Pre-Pro, 1929-1991 (Folder 129)
  - Prospective Students, 1959-1961 (Folder 130)
  - Public Relations, 1957-1961 (Folder 131)
  - Public Relations, 1962-1963 (Folder 132)
  - Pul-Put, 1929-1991 (Folder 133)
  - Radio, 1956-1963 (Folder 134)
  - Rae-Reck, 1929-1991 (Folder 135)
  - Records, 1957-1964 (Folder 136)
  - Recruiting, 1929-1991 (Folder 137)
  - Red, 1929-1991 (Folder 138)
  - Reed, 1935-1972 (Folder 139)
  - Reed, 1973-1989 (Folder 140)
  - Reid-Ren, 1929-1991 (Folder 141)
  - Rex-Rid, 1929-1991 (Folder 142)
  - Rie-Riz, 1929-1991 (Folder 143)
  - Roa-Roc, 1929-1991 (Folder 144)
  - Rog-Row, 1929-1991 (Folder 145)
  - Rue-Rus, 1929-1991 (Folder 146)
  - Rut-Ryl, 1929-1991 (Folder 147)
  - Sab-Sar, 1929-1991 (Folder 148)
  - Sau-Schoe, 1929-1991 (Folder 149)
  - Scholarships, 1952-1960 (Folder 150)
  - Scholarships, 1961-1963 (Folder 151)
  - Scholarships, 1964 (Folder 152)
  - Scholarships: Dudley White, 1951-1952 (Folder 153)
  - Scholarships: Dudley White, 1953-1960 (Folder 154)
  - Scholarships: Dudley White, 1961-1966 (Folder 155)
  - Schr-Schu, 1929-1991 (Folder 156)
  - Schwab, 1968-1977 (Folder 157)
  - Schwab, 1978-1988 (Folder 158)
  - Schwartz-Scr, 1929-1991 (Folder 159)
  - Scu-Sel, 1929-1991 (Folder 160)
  - Seminars, 1959 (Folder 161)
  - Seminars Assemblies 1-2, 1929-1991 (Folder 162)
  - Seminars assemblies 3-4, 1929-1991 (Folder 163)
  - Ses-Sha, 1929-1991 (Folder 164)
  - She-Shir, 1929-1991 (Folder 165)
  - Shivel, 1929-1991 (Folder 166)
  - Sho-Sie, 1929-1991 (Folder 167)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1926-1960 (Folder 168)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1961-1962 (Folder 169)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1962-1964 (Folder 170)
  - Sim- D. Smith, 1929-1991 (Folder 171)
  - H. Smith- Ra. Smith, 1929-1991 (Folder 172)
  - Ro. Smith-Smy, 1929-1991 (Folder 173)
  - SNPA, 1929-1991 (Folder 174)
  - Sny-Som, 1929-1991 (Folder 175)
  - Speakers: Arm-Cole, 1929-1991 (Folder 176)
  - Speakers: Cols-Gol, 1929-1991 (Folder 177)
  - Speakers:Hal-Hou, 1929-1991 (Folder 178)
  - Speakers: Kel-Lau, 1929-1991 (Folder 179)
  - Speakers: Mar-Nag, 1929-1991 (Folder 180)
  - Speakers: Nat-Rei, 1929-1991 (Folder 181)
  - Speakers: Sag-Wil; Misc., 1929-1991 (Folder 182)
  - Spen-Spilman, 1929-1991 (Folder 183)
  - Spilman-Spit, 1929-1991 (Folder 184)
  - Sta-Ste, 1929-1991 (Folder 185)
  - Sti-Strassoldo, 1929-1991 (Folder 186)
  - Strassoldo, 1969 (Folder 187)
  - Strassoldo-Szl, 1929-1991 (Folder 188)
  - Tai-Tat, 1929-1991 (Folder 189)
  - Tay-The, 1929-1991 (Folder 190)
  - Thi-Tin, 1929-1991 (Folder 191)
  - Tob- B. Trussel, 1929-1991 (Folder 192)
  - W. Trussel, 1959-1974 (Folder 193)
  - W. Trussel, 1974-1984 (Folder 194)
  - W. Trussel, 1984-1989 (Folder 195)
  - Try-Tur, 1929-1991 (Folder 196)
  - United States Information Agency, 1957-1958 (Folder 197)
  - United States Information Agency, 1958-1960 (Folder 198)
  - United States Information Agency, 1960-1964 (Folder 199)
  - University of Virginia, 1929-1991 (Folder 200)
  - Vad-Ver, 1929-1991 (Folder 201)
  - virginia Press Association, 1932-1960 (Folder 202)
  - virginia Press Association, 1961 (Folder 203)
  - virginia Press Association, 1961-1962 (Folder 204)
  - virginia Press Association, 1962 (Folder 205)
  - virginia Press Association, 1963 (Folder 206)
  - virginia Press Association, 1964-1965 (Folder 207)
  - Virginia Social Science Association-Vos, 1929-1991 (Folder 208)
  - Wad-Wal, 1929-1991 (Folder 209)
  - War Wat, 1929-1991 (Folder 210)
  - Wea-Wes, 1929-1991 (Folder 211)
  - Wet-Whe, 1929-1991 (Folder 212)
  - Whitc-White, 1929-1991 (Folder 213)
  - White, 1929-1991 (Folder 214)
  - Whitman-Wilk, 1929-1991 (Folder 215)
  - A. William-C.Williams, 1929-1991 (Folder 216)
  - C. Williams-M.Williams, 1929-1991 (Folder 217)
  - S. Williams-Witt, 1929-1991 (Folder 218)
  - Witt-D.Wolfe, 1929-1991 (Folder 219)
  - T. Wolfe-Wood, 1929-1991 (Folder 220)
  - Wor-WSLS, 1929-1991 (Folder 221)
  - Zas-Zilahly, 1929-1991 (Folder 222)
  - Zilahy, 1929-1991 (Folder 223)
  - Misc., 1929-1991 (Folder 224)
  - Unprocessed Materials, 1929-1993 (Box 4a)
- Personal Publicity, 1937-1977; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); .417 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 1-37)
  Items in this series consist primarily of articles, bulletins, memos, and programs which are in reference to O.W. Riegel and his career achievements. The material spans the majority of his professional carreer and makes reference to his published works, acts as a staff member of Washington and Lee, and personal achievements. The publicity material is primarily newspaper clippings selected by Riegel himself.
  Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold)
  - Personal Publicity, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Personal Publicity, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Personal Publicity, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Personal Publicity, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Personal Publicity, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Personal Publicity, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Personal Publicity, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Personal Publicity, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Personal Publicity, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Personal Publicity, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Personal Publicity, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Personal Publicity, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Personal Publicity, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Personal Publicity, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Personal Publicity, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Personal Publicity, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Personal Publicity, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Personal Publicity, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Personal Publicity, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Personal Publicity, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Personal Publicity, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Personal Publicity, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Personal Publicity, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Personal Publicity, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Personal Publicity, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Personal Publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Personal Publicity, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Personal Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Personal Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Personal Publicity, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Personal Publicity, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Personal Publicity, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Personal Publicity, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Personal Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Personal Publicity, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)